Resha Puspita Dewi

Portfolio | LinkedIn | GitHub | Tech Stacks

Location: Bandung, West Java, Indonesia Email: reshapuspitadewi@gmail.com | Mobile: +6282130320607

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

I am a detail-oriented and motivated individual, driven by a genuine curiosity and passion for software development. I have gained proficiency in **React.js and Tailwind CSS**, as well as familiarity with **Node.js, MongoDB, and Next.js**. My internship experiences has sharpened my critical thinking skills and taught me to keep the user in mind while developing products.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Java, Kotlin, Ruby

Frameworks : React.js, Next.js, Express, Node.js, Tailwind CSS

Libraries : Framer Motion, Redux Toolkit, React Router, React Query

Databases : MongoDB

Dev Tools: Visual Studio Code, Git, Postman, REST Client

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

Sagara Technology

WFO - Bandung, West Java, Indonesia

- Acquired proficiency in utilizing technologies such as AntDesign and Next.js
- Participated in project execution, including bug fixing using Postman, UI slicing using Figma, and implementing features in both internal and client project using React.js and Tailwind CSS
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams, resulting in improved product quality and user experience

UX Designer Intern

Feb 2022 - May 2022

Prosa.ai

Remote - Bandung, West Java, Indonesia

- Learned about design thinking and best practices in UX design, applying new knowledge to design projects using tool such as **Figma and UsabilityHub**
- Conducted a usability study for a newly launched product, recruiting 10 participants within two-weeks time-frame
- · Worked closely with the product manager to discuss design and interaction requirements

EDUCATION

Institut Teknologi Bandung

Bachelor of Science in Information System and Technology

August 2017 – March 2023

TRAINING AND CERTIFICATIONS

Generasi Gigih Participant (2021) - Backend Developer Path

Certificate

- Generasi GIGIH by Yayasan Anak Bangsa Bisa (YABB) provides various training programs for tech talents, including a back-end development path that focuses on Ruby as the primary programming language
- Acquired skills: Ruby, Backend Development, RSpec, unit testing

Bangkit Academy Batch 1 (2021) - Mobile Android Development Path

Certificate

- The program initiated by Google, GoTo, Traveloka offers mobile development training for Android developers, with a focus on using Kotlin as the main programming language.
- Acquired skills: Java, Kotlin, Mobile Development

Digital Talent Incubator (DTI) 2020 - Backend Developer Talent

Certificate

- Telkom Digital Talent Incubator (DTI) 2020 is a Digital Skill Development Program intended for final year stundents
 carried out by PT Telkom in collaboration with Telkom University. I was chosen to be a talent on the Back End
 Developer skillset and learn about backend development.
- Acquired skills: Express, Node.js, SQL, MySQL

Web Development Bootcamp Graduate (2020)

Certificate

- Impact Byte's Web Development Bootcamp is designed to give students a comprehensive understanding of web development, from the front end to the back end. Over the course of the bootcamp, I built final projects using technologies such as React, Node.js, and Express, as well as database management with MongoDB.
- Acquired skills: React.js, Node.js, Express, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Git, Bootstrap, Styled-Components, Bulma, Material UI